No, I was going to be a jackass,
but I stopped myseIf.
(Leonard:)I stayed a good guy,
so I'm gonna pass on the sex.
(Leonard:)But you should know,
that's not a comment on your hotness...
(Leonard:)...but on my goodness.
(Leonard:)That's kind of my superpower.
I'm... I'm like Captain Good Guy.
(Leonard:)It's okay. Did the right thing.
(Leonard:)You idiot!
- Hey, Priya.
- Hey, sweetheart. How's it going?
(Leonard:)Uh. Not so good. We have to talk.
(Priya:)Oh. Sounds serious. What's up?
(Leonard:)Okay, uh, here it is.
I met this girI and I kissed her
and I feel terrible about it.
(Leonard:)But it's done,
it's never gonna happen again...
(Leonard:)...and I am so, so sorry.
(Priya:)Leonard, relax. It's okay.
- It is?
- Yeah, these things happen.